[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Is it nice?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "My first husband.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "How was that?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "I married him.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "ORGAN: Did you really?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "Better.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "And was he as good as you thought he would be?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Refrigerators.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "I mean how have you kept so remarkably youthful, ladies?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Fresh air.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "Anyone else?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "Being happy?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "You never went there?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Stephen Sondheim was on PBS for his birthday celebration and he -- after the whole night, he took the microphone and he said, first you're young, then you're middle-aged, and then you're wonderful.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "Angela, what do you think?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "But is it true?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Well, I never looked at life as if I was a sex symbol so I didn't place myself in that --", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "When you're no longer that kind of sex symbol, what is it like for you psychologically?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "Sad.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "How did you feel to hear that?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Yes, because it was the truth.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "I like the aging process because I've gotten a kind of freedom from it.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "What it's been like, the aging process, I guess?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "I don't speak numbers.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "But you were this stunning operation in \"Star Trek\" and electrified the world of TV, what's it been like for you?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "And that's annoying, isn't it?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "I told everyone my age.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "NIDENTIFIED FEMALE: Oh, sure.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Have any of you lied about your age over the years?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "102.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "What are the crucial ages for a woman to start telling fibs, do you think?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "I think 60's brutal.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "I think that's probably true, isn't it?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "60.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "I mean should anyone talk about this in public?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "So talk to me about -- have you ever had it?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "I think if you go to the right doctor and you -- first, if you want it.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "And what do you think?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "VANS: Really in each of us I think each person does it for different reasons.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Is it pressure from men do you think that they want to see affection in women even if they get older?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Do you regret it or are you pleased?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "It wasn't to make him stick around.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Did it stick around?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "I think if you -- it's wonderful, it's a technology that's there for you if you need it, if you want it.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "What do you think, Nichelle?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "I had -- my nose broken in a car accident and I was never happy with my nose.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Have you been tempted?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "No, not -- oh, yes, I'm guilty.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "Is that a guilty run?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "ICKINSON: Usually I've had girls coming to me and say -- coming crying, oh my god, I don't look like myself at all.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "You don't?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Well, I think that there's a time in an actress' life when she's making certain transitions when you're in the middle of that -- of those transitions where you're still playing leading roles but maybe there is a little puff under the eyes or a little something that's consistently catching the light and when it does it's distracting, because there -- you know, the perception of beauty, we get the perception of beauty off the cover of magazines.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Stephanie, what's your view of surgery?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Pretty much.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Are they professional imperative, I mean, if you don't have this kind of work, particularly in America?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "They mean get a little something --", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "What they mean is get down to the surgeon, right?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "I didn't need it then.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "I mean, what do you think of that picture?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "I feel brave because it was I think 1965 or '66.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "When you look at that picture, what do you feel?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "I mean it was outrageous at the time, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "I loved it.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Did you like that?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "It's an honor and I'm not fooled by how I look and what my age is.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Sean Connery.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Nichelle?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "I think he gets more beautiful as he gets older.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Why Sean Connery?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Have you met, Sean?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "I got as close as I could.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "And did you get anywhere with it or not?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Johnny Depp for sure.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Linda, how about you?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "I don't think there's anything about him that's a toy boy.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Little pirate toy boy, huh?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Have you met Johnny Depp?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Would you like to?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Well, I'm happy he's married and he's got his life --", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "If he's watching, have you got a message for him?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "I think you're happy about that at all, right?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "No --", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Can't you jump to Stephanie?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Who could tell me stories and have that -- you know, brilliant.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "No, no, it isn't -- it wasn't -- the choice was not based on sex.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "You wouldn't want sex for Johnny Depp?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Could you imagine?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Waking up to Winston Churchill with a cigar?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "Gosh, well, my first thought of course was Bill Holden.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Stephanie, how about you?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Maybe I could have convinced him not to go on to Russia.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "He was only about 5'3\", wasn't he?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Frank.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Who's been the great love of your life?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Frank Sinatra?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Because he was smashing.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Why frank?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Wasn't he?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Was he as great as I imagined him to be?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Was he good with women, do you think?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Not all.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "Yes, I know this for sure.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "You know this for sure?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "I don't want to answer that because he was the great love of my life.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "In your case who would be the great love of your life?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "ICHOLS: I don't know that that's so.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "When you have that kind of love, and then you lose it, do you -- can you ever get it back from anybody else?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Well, I've been fortunate in that I loved my first husband so much, but I would say Yanni --", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "Who would be the love of your life?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "-- would be the love of my life.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "Oh, well, of course, I think that William Holden came into my life at a time in my life and in his life that was an extremely strong connection.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Stefanie?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "When he actually kissed me, the director says, cut, cut, cut.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "Were you aware at the time of how significant it was going to be?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "You've asked the wrong person.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "Was it as hard as it seems now looking back on that era?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "I've had a career that should never be because I didn't want to be an actress.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "I had every gun (INAUDIBLE).", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "Oh, no, you had a gun, didn't you?", "qSentId": 721}, {"answer": "I just felt exhausted.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 737, "question": "Did you feel like you were making a bit of a stand here?", "qSentId": 736}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "When you see the young actresses today, do you think they have it easier, really, than you had it?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "Now you can't breathe without having everything out there.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 759, "question": "When you have to lead your life in a goldfish bowl of fame, how much harder is it when you go through the tough times in life, do you think, to be famous and going through it with everybody having an eye on what's going on?", "qSentId": 758}, {"answer": "(voice-over): Yes, really.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 776, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 775}, {"answer": "No, that's not what's bugging me.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 783, "question": "Is that what's bugging you?", "qSentId": 782}, {"answer": "There's getting along and friends.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 801, "question": "I mean, are you friends or not really?", "qSentId": 800}, {"answer": "Well, that's what I mean.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 805, "question": "How can you ever be friendly with anyone again after that?", "qSentId": 804}, {"answer": "Barbara Stanwick taught me to do stunts when I did \"Big Valley.\"", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 814, "question": "Are you a bit fiery in real life?", "qSentId": 813}, {"answer": "I never slapped anybody except on \"Dynasty\" ever, ever.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 817, "question": "ORGAN: Did you use it on a man before?", "qSentId": 816}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 830, "question": "And when you actually do those things, would you actually whack each other or not?", "qSentId": 829}, {"answer": "That would not work well.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 835, "question": "-- try and get one through just to, you know, assert your authority?", "qSentId": 834}, {"answer": "When I flew with the Blue Angels.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 857, "question": "Linda?", "qSentId": 856}, {"answer": "I mean, no, I didn't get sick.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 869, "question": "And then you're sick, right?", "qSentId": 868}, {"answer": "I think of three in my whole life.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 877, "question": "Nichelle?", "qSentId": 876}, {"answer": "In Thousand Oaks, out where it was dark.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 895, "question": "Where were you?", "qSentId": 894}, {"answer": "I'm afraid it's over.", "docId": "110206pmt", "aSentId": 906, "question": "Is it over?", "qSentId": 905}]